-宝贝  -怎么了
- Honey? - Yeah?
我告诉过你  拥有你我是如此幸运吗
Have I told you how lucky I am to have you?
歌洛莉亚  借过
Gloria, excuse me.
我发自内心这么认为
'Cause I am.
好吧
Okay.
-祝你...  -不要唱歌
- Hap-- ? - No singing.
这蛋糕怎么变成这样了
What the hell happened to the cake?
没有啊  挺漂亮的啊
Nothing. It's beautiful.
好了  咱们来拆礼物吧
Okay, let's open the presents.
没错  礼物礼物  礼物礼物
Yes! Presents! Presents! Presents! Presents!
-先拆谁的  -我先来  先拆我的
- Who's first? - Mine first. Mine first.
您知道的  克莱尔跟我--
And as you know, Claire and I--
我们的礼物还没完成
we didn't quite finish ours,
不过我们会尽速做好给您补上的
but we will be getting that to you.
好的
Fine.
我们的礼物本来是满瓶的红酒和一张生日卡
And our gift is a fuller version of that and a card.
很好
Wonderful.
当然了  这个蛋糕  是...是我的
And, of course, the cake is, uh, mine.
真不错
Fantastic.
然后这里还有一个
And here we have a phone...